There's no way that
a mouse could kill a scorpion.
A mouse's got sharp claws and teeth.
- A rat can kill a scorpion.
- No shit,
we're not talking about a rat,
but about a little mouse.
A rat still would lose.
A little mouse fighting a scorpion.
And that is final!
Stop!
Shut up!
Oh, my God, I don't care.
All we're doing is arguing about
the most stupid shit!
A rat, a scorpion, I don't care, man!
When did this start happening?
When did we start arguing all
the time and fighting?
This isn't like us.
Look, we're working our asses
off in this bar, you know,
we're getting nothing to show for it,
so we're starting to snip
and pick at each other, it's bullshit.
'Cause guess what?
It's a beautiful day outside, okay?
We need to change things up.
Let's go outside.
Let's get some fresh air.
Let's run around a little bit,
you know?
Let's just do something different.
You know what, Charlie,
you're right, this is great.
It's nice to do something
different for a change.
Yeah, enjoy a little blue sky,
some fresh air.
Some Earth beneath our feet.
- See, I told you guys you'd like it.
- Yeah.
It's goddamn bright out here.
- It's so bright. It hurts my eyes.
- It's blinding!
- People are playing football.
- It's like there's no room to drink.
I would like to go back to the bar.
Let's go back to the bar.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, look out.
Can I get that back?
Yeah, go long and I'll toss
you a wicked spiral.
Wanna just give me the ball, dude?
We're trying to practice.
- What are you practicing for?
- I'm trying out for the Eagles.
- Uh, the Philadelphia Eagles?
- Yeah.
They're holding tryouts
for the public.
Like in that movie, Invincible.
The one with the guy from the New Kids
on the Block makes it onto the Eagles?
- I saw that.
- That's the one.
A good one.
So they're actually doing that?
Just give me the football.
Well, Dennis, I think you
know what we have to do.
Transcript: www.swsub.com
Subtitles: Ju
www.top-series.net
Episode 3x02
Did you read this flyer?
Donovan McNabb is going to be
giving us a motivational speech.
I know, dude. We are actually going
to be running on the Linc.
Lincoln Field, baby.
You think you're gonna make the team?
Hell, no, we're not. But we will
finally get to prove once and for all
who's the better football player.
Trying out for the Eagles
is the best way to settle that score.
I would like to join
your little competition.
You're a woman!
Women can't do things like this,
you'll get hurt.
- Women aren't allowed to try out.
- Well, that's ridiculous.
They should at least
be able to try out.
Well, there are plenty of other sports
that women can try out for.
Like cooking and...
Complaining to your friends
about your boyfriends.
Playing at ballet...
Cleaning, displaying cars at
auto shows in tiny bikinis.
Yeah, when you get older
you can play bridge together.
You know what? I am in such better
shape than both of you guys.
The first thing they're gonna do
to weed people out is to make you run?
Oh, good luck.
I could get so much further than
both of you.
Do you think that's a possibility?
That could be very embarrassing.
Well, we're never going to have
to find out because she can't try out.
- You can't try out!
- That is a rule, right?
Check the rules.
A layer of beer, then a layer of ice.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
- We're going to tailgate the tryouts.
- Shit, that's a good idea.
- You're gonna bust out Green Man?
- No Green Man.
What's Green Man?
In high school, Charlie was
like our school mascot.
A mascot nobody wanted.
He'd get wasted and dress in
this green spandex bodysuit.
Spandex?
That's it, you've got to
bring the Green Man suit.
No, Green Man was good,
it got me through some hard times,
but I'm done with it.
You can wear it if you want,
but I'm just gonna be relaxing.
It's gonna be about
chilling out for me.
No, this is going to be
exactly like Woodstock.
Is it? Are you planning on getting
yourself locked in the bathroom
of your cousin's Winnebago for 3 days?
Shut up about that.
I survived on hand soap and
toilet water for three days.
The memory haunts me.
The Linc, dude, the Linc!
I am actually gonna be able
to look down
and literally see how many yards
I'm running.
- This is gonna be awesome, dude.
- We might actually get further
in this tryout than we thought.
See how many yahoos are trying out?
- I'm seeing a lot wearing capes.
- There are like 15 guys wearing capes.
Why would you wear a cape?
What advantage does that give you?
Absolutely none. You know what?
Have a little respect.
We're here with the Philadelphia Eagles,
they're opening up their doors to us.
- This is a boyhood dream.
- I know, why even come out here
if you're not gonna take this
somewhat seriously? I mean...
- You done pissing yet?
- I haven't even started,
you're standing next to me,
talking to me,
- it's making me nervous.
- All right, another beer?
Yeah, another beer for Christ's sake.
Gonna sit here and not drink another?
Yeah.
Okay, the cabana is assembled,
the grill is as sparkling
as we're gonna get it,
the margarita machine here
is open for business.
Time to relax.
Want to drop some acid with me?
What?
You're dropping acid?
Woodstock, baby!
Okay, well, no, thank you.
I believe that we'd have the complete
opposite effect of relaxation for me.
Well, I'm going to trip balls.
You messed it up. It's too high.
It doesn't look right.
Too high? No, I'm good at it.
I did a good job on you.
'Cause I've good cheekbones.
- You have?
- Yeah.
'Cause you put foundation all over them.
I put a light base on...
just a, it's got SPF.
What's up?
- What the hell is this?
- How's it hangin'?
- This is a joke, right?
- You think anyone's gonna buy that?
- Whatever, bro.
- You're gonna get crushed.
The second that your body touches that
field, it's gonna shatter like glass.
- You got bones like glass.
- I don't.
You spent half your life
in a back brace.
Your body is like 90% scoliosis, Dee.
Line's moving, fellas.
Let's get on the bus.
Bus? What the hell
are you talking about?
The bus that takes you to the field.
I thought we were gonna be
playing on the Linc.
You think you dipshits are gonna play on
the same field that champions play on?
Where we going?
"Where we going?"
We're going to a shitty high
school in Bucks County.
Now get your ass on the bus.
If I say it one more time...
If I say it one more time!
Sprint to the bus.
That's everyone on the bus, dude.
They're leaving.
Maybe they're having tryouts
at a different place.
Son of a bitch.
All right, screw it, man,
we're here, we'll just relax.
Sit here and look at the
Linc?
We look like a couple of dicks
in the yard. Get out of here!
We got to get up and go.
Let's go follow that bus! Come on!
All right, you get that.
You get that, come on.
- This is too much work.
- Charlie, get up!
- This is work! I didn't want to go.
- Get the stuff, we'll follow the bus.
I like your mustache.
- Thank you.
- I can't grow one.
Okay.
- That's a pretty sweet cape.
- Thank you.
My mom made it.
- She did a very good job.
- Yeah, she's talented.
I can't believe we're not gonna be
on the Linc. This is bullshit.
Half the reason I wanted to do this,
was to be out on that field.
Hey, man, stop smoking, will you?
Some of us are trying to make the team.
- Are you kidding me, bro?
- No.
Guy, if you think you're actually going
to make the Philadelphia Eagles,
then you're pathetic.
- You're pathetic.
- No, you're pathetic, sport.
- You're pathetic!
- You're the one who's pathetic!
Whatever, man.
When I'm done with this tryout, you'll
go back to your sad, pitiful life,
and I'll be on the Eagles.
And everybody in Philadelphia
will know the name McPoyle.
- What did you say your name was?
- McPoyle. Doyle McPoyle.
The unibrow.
Yeah.
- The unibrow.
- Yeah.
- The eczema...
- He's definitely a McPoyle.
There are so many of those people.
Now, this is what I'm talking about!
- I don't know.
- Look at all the people!
W're stuck over here by the portable
shitters. That's kind of lame.
Stop bitching and set up.
I'm not setting anything up.
I'm sitting in my chair,
I'm relaxing, I'm getting blackout drunk
and you're leaving me alone.
All right, be a party pooper.
- What are you doing, dude?
- Taking more acid.
Classic mistake, Frank.
You're making a classic mistake,
you know.
Will you shut up and sit in
your stupid chair?
It's your funeral, buddy.
- Just shut up.
- Hey there, guy.
That's good, that's good.
Are you kidding me, man?
What the hell is that shit?
Come on, dude.
You almost ran me...
- Oh, my God, the McPoyle brothers.
- Hello, Charles.
- What are you doing here?
- We came to support our brother Doyle.
He's going to make the
Eagles.
- Well, that's fantastic.
- Whatever man. That's great.
But your bus is spilling over
into our space.
- You almost ran me over, man.
- You got to move.
- Move it back a few feet.
- No.
No can do. We need the space.
For what?
The whole family's here.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, my God, are you kidding me?
Great, of course...
How many...?
What is that a jar of?
What is that a jar of, dude?
How many can there possibly be?
Oh, good to see her again. Good.
She doesn't know what I'm saying, right?
Oh, here he comes.
Yeah, you're here in the world.
That's the sun.
- It's going to hurt your eyes.
- Watch your mouth.
What is that, a fife?
You brought your little flute.
Is there more? Are there any more?
Get them all out.
All right, look, I tell you what.
Leave me alone, okay?
I don't care what you do.
Just leave me alone,
'cause I'm here to relax
and have a good time,
I don't your shit, all right?
So, leave me alone, okay?
We be cool. We're even now.
- Bump it.
- I'm not bumping your fist.
- Do it, bump it.
I'm not bumping you, all right? I never
bumped 'em once, and I'm not gonna...
All right, whatever. No bumping.
I just don't want to.
These guys are freak shows, man.
- Hustle up!
- Hustle, brother!
Let's go, bitches.
Let's move it!
I was here first, Coach.
- Hustle!
- Coach, hi! Hi, there.
Cole. Cole Armstrong.
Three-time All-American fastest
sprinter in five counties, Coach.
Would you like us to stand when you
address us, or to take a knee?
I don't give a shit!
Okay.
I'll take a knee.
We're doing these trials for you!
Because of your harassment
and your love for the New Kids
on the Block movie.
You paid the $30 fee.
We promised you a keynote speaker.
All right, bring him up.
McNabb, dude!
McNabb!
Gentlemen!
- Uh, this good here?
- Yeah, that's cool.
Just put your parking brake on.
Donovan McNabb.
Hey, guys.
I'm Donovan McNabb.
Uh, I played quarterback for the
Philadelphia Eagles,
and I'm here to tell you
that you can, too,
if you start every day with a hearty
breakfast from McDonalds.
Uh, like the new sausage-egg
McGriddle value meal,
available now for a limited time
for under $5.00.
Uh, remember, guys, real champs
eat at McDonalds.
I'm lovin' it.
Can I get the check?
- What the hell was that?
- Thanks, Donny.
- That wasn't Donovan McNabb.
- That was not him!
- That was like a McDonald's plug.
- Was that the guy fromThe Cosby Show?
That's not the guy fromThe
Cosby Show.
- Yeah, he was married to Sondra.
- Alvin! Alvin!
They had Raven Symone. That's So Raven.
That is not the guy from...
You know what?
Sprints!
Goddamn it!
Good job, dude.
I'm starting to feel it.
- I bet you are, bud.
- Feeling weird.
Yeah, you're probably
feeling very weird.
The acid's making me feel
like I got to take a dump.
That's what happens
when you take a lot of acid.
I got to go.
- Then go.
- The line is too long.
- Maybe I can't hold it in.
- Then go in the McPoyle's camper.
Oh, no.
That might bring back bad memories.
I think I'm going to hold it.
- How are you feeling?
- Annoyed.
- There's nothing kicking in yet?
- What are you talking about, the beer?
No, the acid.
I did not take any acid, remember?
Oh, yeah, you did.
What are you talking about?
I put a shitload of it in your beer.
- What?!
- Yeah.
Is that why those pieces of papers
were floating in my beer?
I drank all that shit, dude.
There was like a ton of acid in there!
Why did you do that?
I don't wanna be the only one tripping.
Oh, my God!
- I actually really have to go...
- Oh, my God!
Shut up! I don't care.
Go in their camper.
Get out of here!
Oh, you sick son of a bitch, dude.
Why would you...?
Oh, shit. Oh, shit!
- You ready to quit yet, Cole?
- You had enough yet, Cole?
Yeah, Cole.
- You ran for ten minutes.
- My side is going to explode.
You're in terrible shape.
This is gonna be easier than I thought.
- Let's go! Move it, come on.
- Oh, so much pain.
All right, now we've got
our hearts pumping.
Let's pick out some gear,
pick a partner... hitting drill!
I pick Cole.
Oh, no, he did it.
That's my dance.
That's my signature dance.
I wanna do that when I tackle people.
I like your form, I liked how you went
before the whistle.
- Goddamn right.
- Nice.
All right, guys,
let's pick new partners.
Eenie, meanie, miney, mo.
Nice. All right, you're up, man.
Hitting's not really my thing, Coach.
Spoken like a true champion.
You just might make the team.
- Awesome. Really?
- Jesus Christ.
Okay, Frank, that was easy...
now just exit, don't talk to anybody.
These people are freak shows.
Wait... better wash your hands.
No telling what kind of germs
these McPoyles have.
I'm starting to feel weird.
What the hell? Not again.
Oh, no! Hey!
Somebody get me out of here!
Man, my brother just leveled
your boy out there.
He's going to make the Eagles.
Your boy is a pansy,
but Doyle's a big, strong guy.
'Cause he eats all that fish.
Is he just going to talk at me?
I am going to lose my shit.
What's going on with his head?
It's too small
or tight or something.
Yeah, that's it.
His skin is too tight.
My skin's not tight.
Good catch, Doyle!
Good catch! Way to hustle!
Way to hustle!
All right, who's next?
This guy.
All right, run out and hook
in.
Run out and hook in. Show these people
how to play football.
I'm going to make Mac look so bad.
My form is perfect.
I'm like Jerry Rice.
Feel that stride.
So fluid and fast.
I've got the stride of a gazelle...
a beautiful, beautiful gazelle person.
My body is achieving a perfect
symmetry right now.
It's that long, lean muscle I've
worked so hard to achieve.
I should have popped my shirt off.
Goddamn it, I really should have
popped that shirt off.
I wonder if any women are
watching from the sidelines.
All right, Dee, you can do this.
You can kick a football.
You're better at sports
than Mac and Dennis.
Holy shit!
The other coach has got to hear
about this.
Well, well, look who's a natural.
Guess I'll be getting further
than you, after all.
- Maybe it was a lucky kick?
- No.
Those stork-like legs,
they act like pendulums,
and on the bottoms of those
pendulums, feet like wrecking balls.
We got to do something
about this, dude.
Let's go talk to Frank.
Come on, I got an idea.
Somebody!
Somebody help!
Goddamn it!
Goddamn it, not again!
Frank.
Hey, Frank.
Who said that?
I'm Artemis. I'm Dee's friend.
- I'm trapped.
- I know,
but I can help.
Crawl into my mouth.
I don't think I could fit.
Sure you will.
Just go one leg at a time.
Okay.
Into the toilet I go.
Man, this is crazy. You are dancing
with the entire McPoyle family.
These people are freak
shows, man. Freaks.
But you're keeping your cool,
you're keeping your cool.
You know why?
Because you are the Green Man.
Green Man is saving your life
right now, bro.
Just go with the flow.
Charlie, we've been looking
all over for you, dude.
Green Man, I knew you couldn't resist.
Huh?
I'm actually tripping
pretty hard right now.
You're tripping?
Yeah, Frank gave me some acid
and it's like... whoo!
Hey, guys.
Guess who got invited
to training camp.
We're going to be famous.
Look, we need to talk to Green Man
alone for a second.
Thank you? Yes, bye.
Can we talk to the Green Man?
Let's go. Thank you.
- Where is Frank? It's very important.
- Really important.
Oh, Frank?
Oh, he's standing right there.
Frank, what the hell are you doing?
He's been trying to climb through
that trash can for 20 minutes.
I'm pretty sure he's on acid.
Thank God, you guys are here.
How'd you get in here?
What are you talking about?
- I've been stuck for 3 hours.
- I think he took a dump in there.
- Can you give us a second, please?
- Whatever.
I'm getting tired
of watching him anyway.
Frank, listen.
Did you bring your gun today?
Great. Now walk me through the plan.
The plan is:
I get close to Dee, all right.
She goes to punt the ball,
I fire, it'll startle her,
- she'll blow the kick.
- Great plan.
Wait a second. How long have we
been standing right here?
- Like, two seconds.
- Seriously?
Frank, give me the gun.
We're in a hurry.
- Where is it?
- In your hand.
Wait, wait!
When the hell did I put Green Man on?
- I don't know.
- That lizard talks!
Where?! I don't like lizards!
We don't have time.
Frank, give us the gun!
Lizard, am I standing in poop?
I'm about to demonstrate to all of you
my natural abilities as a punter.
I'm gonna kick this ball 60 yards right
in front of your faces,
and I'm gonna do it...
as a woman.
Oh, that's right.
I'm a woman!
And I'm about to show all of you
that women should be allowed
to try out for
the Philadelphia Eagles. Coach?
Wrap your minds around this.
Damn!
Oh, I broke my...
Oh, I maybe broke it.
Oh, sweet Jesus, I think I broke it.
- Keep your legs.
- All right, you're out of the trash.
A deal is a deal. Give us the gun.
Hold on. I'm really peek in here.
Stop pointing the gun at us.
Point it at someone else.
Nobody minds making
a little dance right now.
- Nobody cares of you dancing, Charlie.
- Hey, guys.
Could somebody take me to the hospital?
I'm pretty sure I broke
every single bone in my foot
- punting that football.
- Really?
I didn't make it, but I'd like to go
to the E.R. right now, please.
So your bonesaremade out of glass!
Yes.
No, my bones aren't...
You know what?
It doesn't matter because
I made the furthest, so I win.
I win, because you're the girl
and you got knocked unconscious.
You got crushed, dude.
That is so stupid! Guess what?
I made it the farthest.
- You just shattered every bone...
- What are you talking about?
Holy shit, this thing is loaded.
- My leg!
- Doyle, are you okay?
My leg! Somebody shot my leg!
No!
Oh, that's not good.
No, that could come back
and bite us in the ass.
- Ready? Go.
- Let's go!